swaylocks.com 2012-10-03

# Swaylock's Privacy Policy and Promise

## Swaylock's Network Privacy Policy and Promise

The "Swaylock's Network" refers to the group of sites owned and administered by Swaylock's LLC, including Swaylocks.com and Quivermag.com.

## Our Promise

Swaylock's Network respects your privacy and promises to earn and keep your trust. At Swaylock's Network, we understand the importance of privacy, and we want you to be as comfortable as possible visiting our web site and using its services. All information about you is kept confidential and will not be used in ways that you have not consented, and we will not sell or disclose any information that identifies you to a third party without your explicit approval, except to the extent necessary to comply with applicable law, legal process or in legal proceedings where such information is relevant. 

Questions regarding this policy and our practice should be directed to, by e-mail to feedback@swaylocks.com.

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms and Conditions of use. It tells you what information we collect, how we protect it and what choices you have about how that information is used.

**Under 13**

Policy Swaylock's Network does not allow children under the age of thirteen (13) to register because Swaylock's Network must comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Rule, which prohibits the online collection of personal information from people under 13. 

Please note that any information that you reveal in a public forum (such as a bulletin board or chat room/event) will be seen by third parties not related to Swaylock's Network and is therefore not subject to this privacy policy. Also, if you link to a third party site from Swaylock's Network, any information you reveal on that site is not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should consult the privacy policies of each site you visit.

**Personal Information We Collect**

We collect information in three distinct areas: 1) Alerts subscription 2) Membership enrollment and Profile creation. The information we collect in these areas includes: 

  * Alerts / Newsletter subscription: e-mail address*.
  * Membership enrollment and Profile creation: Name*, Password*, Information about specific interests situation. All personal information is protected by your password.

Required information is indicated by an asterisk*. Provision of all other information is optional. 

We also collect information about your use of our site, directly and through the use of "Cookies." Cookies are small computer files that we transfer to your computer's hard drive that allow us to know how often someone visits our site. This information helps us customize our web site specifically for you and also allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our site and for what purpose. Cookies cannot retrieve personal information from your computer. 

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

Personal Information will not be released to third parties without your explicit permission. Swaylock's Network may provide your information to third parties in aggregate with others' information, which does not allow you to be identified or contacted ("Aggregate Information"). For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of users of our site and the activities they conduct while on our site. We might also inform a automobile company (that may or may not be an advertiser on our site) that "30 percent of our users live east of the Mississippi" or that "25 percent of our users have asked questions about fiberglass." Depending on the circumstances, we may or may not charge for this information. 

**How Swaylock's Network Handles Privacy Internally**

We use industry-standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers where appropriate. Nevertheless, absolute security does not yet exist on the Internet. 

**Your Privacy Choices**

You always have options on our site. You can opt in to or out of any of our e-mail lists. If you'd like to get on an e-mail list (for Surfline's Surf Alerts, for instance, or to receive information about new products from our store), simply go to that area and sign up. If you'd like your name to be taken off, follow the "unsubscribe" directions in any e-mail you receive from us. If you have any questions about how seriously we take your privacy, have a look at the other sections here. 

Cookies: you can always disable cookies on your computer. We don't recommend you disable cookies because some great internet features are enhanced by cookie information, and it's a way for us to make the site better for you. Plus, cookies are alphanumeric designations on your computer hard drive that don't provide us with any personal data. But, it's your choice. The way to do it is to go to your Internet browser (like Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator) and look up "cookies" in the help menu. 

Any other questions? E-mail us at feedback@swaylocks.com. 

**Updating Your Personal Information and Contacting Swaylock's Network**

You can always contact us in order to delete your Personal Information from our systems by e-mailing us at info@swaylocks.com. You can always update the Personal Information that you have provided to us and change your Privacy choices by clicking the "update my information" on the web site. 

**Your Consent**

Swaylock's Network may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to our web site. Your use of the site constitutes acceptance of the provisions of this Privacy Policy and your continued usage after such changes are posted constitutes acceptance of each revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy, please exit the site.
